Guide to the Julian C. Smith papers, 1900-2015.
Smith, Julian C. papers
- Series IV. Teaching & Cornell University
  - Other Courses
    - ChE 421: Organic Chemical Course
      - ChE 421 - Glycerine, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
        Includes notes, transparencies
      - ChE 421 - Monochlorobenzene (MCB), 1979-02-1981-03 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        Includes homework, transparencies, notes
      - ChE 421, 1979-05-1983-01 (Box 4, Folder 28)
        Includes schedules, notes, articles
      - ChE 421 - Tolylene Diisocyanate (TDI), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        Includes notes, transparency
      - ChE 421 - Aniline, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - ChE 421, 1980-05-1981-03 (Box 4, Folder 29)
        Includes schedules, notes
      - ChE 421 - Examinations, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
        Includes quizzes, homework, exams
      - ChE 421 - Benezene & Coal Chemistry, 1981-01 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - ChE 421 - Acetone, 1981-11 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - ChE 421 - UREA, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        Includes transparencies, magazines
      - ChE 421 - Mononitrotoluene (MNT), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - ChE 421, 1982-01 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - ChE 421, 1983-01-1983-05 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        Includes grades, exams, articles, assignments,
    - ChE 432: Unit Operations Lab Course
      - ChE 432 - Style Manuals, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - ChE 432 - Suggested Form of Discussion, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - ChE 432 - Filtration Experiment, 1976-10-1978-10 (Box 4, Folder 35)
        Includes notes, lab data
      - ChE 432, 1976-11-1977-07 (Box 4, Folder 38)
        Includes correspondence, notes, articles, transparencies, experiment design
      - ChE 432 - Writing Tests & Homework, 1977-09-1984-12 (Box 4, Folder 34)
        Includes transparencies, articles, notes
      - M.D. Morris ChE 432 Lectures, 1977-12-1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
        Includes correspondence, notes, schedules, workbook
      - ChE 432 - Heat Transfer, 1982-08-1985-08 (Box 4, Folder 36)
        Includes notes, experiment design
    - ChE 463: Synthetic Fuels
      - Synthetic Fuels Course, 1975-07-1978-04 (Box 4, Folder 39)
        Includes notes, correspondence, transparencies, articles
    - ChE 5041: Non-Resident Lectures
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1964-09-25-1965-03-26 (Box 9, Folder 17)
        Includes schedules
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1965-09-24-1966-04-08 (Box 9, Folder 16)
        Includes schedule, notes
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1966-09-30-1967-03-03 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        Includes schedule, course description
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
        Includes course description
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1969-09-19-1969-12-05 (Box 9, Folder 12)
        Includes notes, course description, schedule
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1969-09-20-1969-12-13 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1970-02-20-1970-12-11 (Box 9, Folder 11)
        Includes course description, correspondence, schedule, business cards
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1971-09-1971-12 (Box 9, Folder 10)
        Includes attendance sheet, course description
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1975-09-12-1975-11-14 (Box 9, Folder 19)
        Includes schedule, notes, correspondence,
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1975-09-22-1976-11-19 (Box 9, Folder 24)
        Includes schedule, correspondence
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1977-08-03-1978-02-15 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Non-Resident Lectures, 1978-09-08-1979-11-16 (Box 9, Folder 22)
        Includes schedule,
    - ChE 565
      - ChE 565 Design Project: Disposal of Excess HCl, 1985-01-23-1985-05 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - ChE 462: Design Course
      - ChE 462 - Design Course, 1973-03-1980-03 (Box 13, Folder 7)
        Includes articles, notes, faculty, schedule
      - ChE 462 - Forecasting, Innovation, Doomsday, 1975-03-10-1980-12-03 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        Includes transparencies, conference materials, articles
      - ChE 462 - Design Course, 1982-02-1982-05 (Box 13, Folder 5)
        Includes diagrams, notes, articles, transparencies
      - ChE 462 - Spring General, 1985-03-07 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        Includes presentations, notes
    - ChE 461
      - ChE 461, 1984-08-1984-12 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        Includes transparencies, class outline, problem set
      - ChE 461 - Handouts, Exams, Problems, 1984-08-1984-12 (Box 13, Folder 9)
        Includes handouts, exams, problems
  - Specialty Topics/Research
    - Dimethyl Amine Plant, 1937-03-1945-06 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Includes papers, patent claims
    - Heat Transfer, 1942-01-1974-04 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Includes bulletins, reports, articles, AIChE presentations
    - Centrifuges, 1942-05-1978-12 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Includes correspondence, AIChE presentations, articles, papers, bulletins
    - Ternary Systems - General, 1949-07-1966-11 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence, journals, papers, notes
    - Final Report: Soil Solidification Research, 1951-09 (Box 10)
      Vol. I - Summarization, Fundamental and Applied Research
    - Final Report: Soil Solidification Research, 1951-09 (Box 10)
      Vol. II - Fundamental Properties, Clay - Water Systems
    - Final Report: Soil Solidification Research, 1951-09 (Box 10)
      Vol. III - Applied Research, Chrome-Lignin Process and Soil Briquetting
    - Cornell Research Grant 5266, 1952-05-13-1953-12-29 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes reports, correspondence
    - Centrifuges - General, 1962-10-1975-01 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence, articles, AIChE presentations
    - Gould - Mixing Study, 1962-12-02-1975-07 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes correspondence, notes, memos
    - Mixing, 1963-05-05-1979-02-05 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence, presentations, articles, papers
    - Dispersers, 1964-02-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Includes transparencies, bulletins, correspondence
    - Sewage Dewatering, 1965-1975-11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Includes bulletins, AIChE meetings, transparencies, presentations
    - Centrifuges - Bulletins, 1967-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Impeller Mixers, 1969-03-1981-11-09 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Includes transparencies, correspondence, articles, bulletins
    - Centrifuges, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Includes transparencies, notes, articles, AIChE centrifuge committee related materials
    - Science, Technology & Society Venezuela, 1971-07-1979-11 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence, notes, proposals, reports
    - n-Butanol, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Venezuela, 1974-03-28-1983-03-14 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence, notes, business cards, poster, articles, memoranda
    - Packed Column Fatigue, 1974-05-09 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - UN Reports, 1974-12-1975-06 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Includes notes, reports
    - Latin American Program, 1975-05-21-1980-06-09 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence, newspapers, materials in Spanish
    - Solids Handling, 1978-11-1986-02 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Includes transparencies, bulletins, newsletters
    - Science, Technology & Society Colombia Visit, 1978-11-20-1980-03-04 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Trip to study Multi-national Corporations contributions to Science & Technology Capabilities of Developing Nations; Includes journal, correspondence, notes, company profiles, reports, summaries, studies
    - Nigeria, 1979-02-27-1980-05-12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Includes notes, correspondence, trip report
    - Science, Technology & Society MNC Proposal, 1979-08-02-1980-01-17 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence, proposal, draft report
    - Venezuela, 1979-10-31-1980-03-05 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence, notes, company profiles,
    - Colombian Companies, 1980-01-14-1980-02-01 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Includes correspondence, business cards, itinerary
    - Latin American Program, 1981-04-02-1981-09-21 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Includes correspondence, paper
  - Lectures Outside Cornell
    - Talks, Seminars, 1947-10-08-1967-04-04 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Heat Transfer - Design at University of Edinburgh, 1954-1971-12 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Science, Engineering, and Engineering Science, 1957-12-30-1960-05-04 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Pfizer & Co, 1959-11-03-1959-12-21 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - California Research Corp. Visit, 1961-11-29-1962-04-13 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Talks to Students, 1963-12-1982-11 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Sabbatical at University of Edinburgh, 1969-02-24-1972-07-31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Luwa Corp., 1973-02-21-1978-09-13 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Energy Talk, 1973-09-19-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Towanda, Pennsylvania
    - DuPont Refresher Course, 1974-10-24-1976-08-18 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Seminar: Long Term Radioactive Waste Disposal, 1976-04-26-1986-10-31 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Norwich, New York
    - Luwa Seminar, 1978-05-25-1978-09-26 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - What's New in Chemical Engineering, 1979-02-07 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Louisville, Kentucky
    - Nuclear Waste Talk, 1986-05-26-1987-01-13 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - University of Arkansas Lecture, 1988-02-1991-04-22 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Fayetteville, Arkansas
- Series V. Patents
  - Traction Aid Patent, 1950-09-26-1968-06-10 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Patent on Chrome Lignin PVA, 1952-09-05-1955-12-19 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Air Swept Drill - Patents, Reprints, Invoices, Miscellaneous Notes, 1953-09-16-1961-02-10 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Patent - Air Swept Drill, 1955-12-12-1956-01-20 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Beaumont - Patent, 1966-08-05-1969-05-29 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Series VI. Consulting
  - B-W Ethanol Plant, undated (Box 12)
  - Z-12 Site Recovery, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes summaries
  - DuPont - Reports, Letters, Notes, & Calculations, 1931-11-03-1975-05-02 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Includes articles, notes, correspondence
  - Jobs - Miscellaneous, 1939-09-07-1955-08-30 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    Includes correspondence, reports
  - DuPont - Repauno Works, 1940-1979-07 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Includes articles, notes
  - Soil Solidification - Reports, 1945-1951-08 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jobs - Danciger Oil Co., 1947-03-01-1949-11-09 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    Includes correspondence, payslips
  - Danciger Correspondence, 1947-03-21-1949-11-09 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    Includes correspondence, charts, notes, articles, contracts, reports
  - Danciger Oil Refining Co. Lab Notebook, 1947-03-25-1948-09-16 (Box 12)
  - Manufacture of Di Methyl Amine, 1947-04-21 (Box 5)
    Prepared for Danciger Oil and Refining Co.
  - Manufacture of Di Methyl Amine, 1947-04-21 (Box 12)
  - Jobs - New York State, 1947-05-07-1948-08-20 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    Includes correspondence
  - NY State Dept. of Commerce Reports, Etc., 1947-06-13-1948-05-14 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Agents for the Separation of Methyl Amines by Extractive Distillation, 1948-08-09 (Box 5)
  - Danciger Oil Refining Co. Lab Notebook, 1948-09-16-1949-10-31 (Box 12)
  - Manufacture of Dorco Solvent, 1948-10-12 (Box 5)
  - Manufacture of Di Methyl Amine, 1948-11-26 (Box 5)
  - Manufacture of Di Methyl Amine, 1949-01-07 (Box 5)
  - Manufacture of Di Methyl Amine, 1949-02-14 (Box 5)
  - G.L.F. Studies Notebook, 1950-1959 (Box 15)
  - Corning Glass Works Standard Columns 4" + 6" ID - Packed & Bubble Types, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Includes technical drawings
  - Glass Exchanger, 1950-02-16-1951-01-30 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    Includes correspondence, charts, notes, invoices, technical drawings
  - U.S. Army Soil Solidification Notebooks, 1950-06-1954-02 (Box 15)
    Count: 2
  - Corning Glass Works Notebook, 1950-06-1959-12 (Box 15)
  - Soil Solidification, 1950-06-16-1993-02-28 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Includes correspondence, reports, proposals
  - Jobs Interchemical Corp. Bound Brook Division, 1950-06-20-1951-03-22 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Includes correspondence, invoices
  - Jobs Corning Glass, 1950-08-10-1960-01-04 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Performance of a 6-Inch Glass Bubble-cap Distilling Column, 1950-08-21 (Box 5)
    Prepared for Corning Glass Works
  - Study of Premixing Equipment Report, 1951-01-25 (Box 12)
    Prepared for Bound Brook Division of Interchemical Corporation
  - Eastman Kodak Co., 1951-03-23-1953-06-16 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Includes correspondence, notes, invoices
  - GLF Proposal & Reports, 1951-04-26-1952-09-10 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Includes correspondence, reports, charts, notes, proposal, photos
  - Jobs - Soil Solidification Project, 1951-06-25 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - GLF Invoice & Receipts, 1951-07-01-1955-06-02 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Army Consulting, 1952-01-30-1972-03-10 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Includes correspondence, reports, standards of conduct for the Army, personnel paperwork, notes, minutes, agendas
  - Laboratory Test Data & Field Log, 1952-06-10-1952-09-10 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Contract number: DA-44-009 eng 1531
  - Southern Production Co., 1952-08-06-1952-11-12 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Includes correspondence, notes, charts, invoices
  - Southern Production Co. Lab Notebook, 1952-08-18-1952-10-15 (Box 12)
  - Chrome-Lignin Process & Soil Solidification Studies, 1952-10-1964-02 (Box 15)
  - Intrusion - Prepakt, 1952-10-01-1954-09-20 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Includes correspondence, notes, report
  - MIT & ERDL Reports, 1952-10-21-1953-03-21 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Production and Field Testing of 500 Tons of Chrome -Lignin Stabilized Soil Briquets, 1952-11 (Box 5)
    Prepared for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers
  - ERDL Conference, 1952-11-20-1952-12-05 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dyer Studies, 1952-12-02-1953-12-15 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chrome-Lignin Research, 1953-01-1957-10-02 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Includes correspondence, papers, notes, computation sheets, soil solidification, data book
  - Invoices, Expense Accounts, Personnel, 1953-01-06-1953-09-03 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hough Soils Engineering Labs, 1953-01-11-1963-01-14 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    Includes correspondence, bulletins, articles, notes
  - Reports, 1953-04-24-1961-09-27 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - California Texas Oil Co. Ltd, 1953-04-25-1953-08-08 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Include correspondence, invoice, chart
  - HSEL Lab Notebook, 1953-11-1954-05 (Box 15)
  - Norwich Pharmacal Co. & Maumee Chemical Co., 1954-08-13-1955-01-31 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Baker Perkins & Philadelphia Gear Mixer Study, 1955-01-04-1956-07-06 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - GLF Urea Study, 1955-02-02-1955-06-02 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Includes correspondence, charts, bulletins, notes
  - U.S. Steel, 1955-03-17-1955-04-07 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1955-05-1955-08 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - DuPont Consulting Contract, 1955-09-06-1963-03-06 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bituminous Coal Research, Inc., 1955-09-15-1955-12-03 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - DuPont Correspondence & Contracts, 1955-09-21-1989-10-31 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Includes correspondence, contracts, articles, notes
  - Rose Gardens Cabins Case, 1955-12-1961-01-19 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence, notes, articles, standards booklets
  - Centrifuges - Roger Williams, Inc., 1955-12-01-1956-02-13 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Includes correspondence, notes, summary
  - Corning Glass - General, 1955-12-22-1964-01-06 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Corning Glass - HCl Absorber, 1956-01-05-1957-06-06 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Royce Chemical Co. - Royce vs. Sharples, 1956-01-18-1958-12-10 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Consulting Inquiries, 1956-02-02-1978-05-12 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Includes correspondence, notes, catalog, reports, articles
  - Rubber World - Editing, 1956-07-09-1958-10-17 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Includes correspondence, notes, chapter drafts
  - Columbia - Westphalia Case, 1956-08 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Includes bulletins, photographs, notes, correspondence
  - Corning Glass Works - Chlorine Cooler, 1956-08-23-1957-07-10 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    Includes correspondence, notes, reports
  - Beet Sugar Study, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Includes mechanical plans, correspondence
  - Work for Corning Glass / Radiant Heaters / Pyrex Heat Exchangers Lab Notebook, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Corning Glass - Radiant Heater Tests, 1957-09-17-1959-07-14 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    Includes correspondence, notes, bulletins, charts
  - Corning Heat Exchanger Study, 1957-09-30-1958-07 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    Includes correspondence, two baffles, charts, bulletins, notes, invoices
  - Consulting - Merck & Co., Inc., 1958-05-15-1958-06-17 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Chicopee Mills Corp., 1958-07-18-1960-09-28 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Includes correspondence, notes, non-woven fabrics packet
  - Expanding Soils - Federal Housing Administration, 1958-08-15-1958-09-05 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Corning Glass - Fume Scrubber, 1959-03-11-1959-12-14 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    Includes correspondence, notes, charts
  - Sewer Explosion Case, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Corning Glass - Mist Eliminator Study, 1961-04-21-1961-07-17 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    Includes correspondence, bulletins
  - Corning Glass - Glass Pump Test, 1961-06-16-1961-08-15 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - DuPont - Jackson Lab, 1961-12-1962-04-13 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Includes correspondence, references
  - Beet Sugar Study - Calculations, 1962-07-1963-08-01 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Includes notes, charts, notebook
  - Beet Sugar - Government Reports, Contract, 1962-12-01-1964-07-15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Includes empty Pioneer Sugar bag, correspondence, contract, reports, notes
  - Modern Design, 1963-03 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kennecott Copper, 1963-09-30-1964-09-28 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Includes correspondence, notes, index to foreign patents
  - Kennecott Copper, 1964-04-28-1966-10-19 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Includes correspondence, notes, patent copies
  - American Metal Climax, 1964-08-12-1965-02-01 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - DuPont Beaumont, 1970-03-03-1986-05-13 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Includes flight itineraries, computation sheets, notes, agendas, correspondence
  - DuPont - Louisville, 1970-06-02-1990-12-21 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Includes correspondence, schedules, notes,
  - PPG - Corpus Christi, 1970-10-12-1971-03-16 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Roto Salt, 1970-11-30-1970-12-30 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Includes correspondence, notes, draft agreement
  - DuPont - Jackson Lab, 1970-12-04-1984-02-16 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Includes correspondence, notes, computation sheets, schedules
  - ARCHO - Contracts, Invoices, 1970-12-30-1977-06-15 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Includes correspondence, contract agreements, invoices
  - Atlantic Richfield Hanford Co., 1971-02-11-1971-06-11 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - DuPont Travel, 1971-05-24-1988-02-04 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Includes flight itineraries, long distance call records, receipts
  - ARCHO - Consultants Committee, 1971-08-10-1973-08-15 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - DuPont - Chambers Works Elastomers, 1972-09-13-1984-03-27 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Includes computation sheets, notes, correspondence, itineraries
  - B.K. Hough, 1972-10-13-1973-10-23 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - DuPont - Pontchartrain, 1973-01-22-1988-11-22 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Includes correspondence, agendas, notes, computation sheets
  - ARCHO, 1973-11-19-1975-11-21 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Includes correspondence, reports, notes
  - Corning Project, 1974-03-11-1974-08-28 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - ARCHO - Consultants Committee, 1974-06-1975-09-19 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Includes correspondence, reports, charts, agendas, notes
  - Sun Chemical Corp., 1974-07-22-1974-09-03 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Includes correspondence, bulletin, notes
  - Inquiry - Gillian, 1975-09-11-1975-11-10 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Includes notes, correspondence
  - ARCHO - 11th Waste Management Meeting, 1975-09-30-1976-05-26 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Includes reports, correspondence, agendas, notes
  - Yarway Corporation, 1975-10-31-1976-03-30 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Includes correspondence, bulletin
  - Long-Term Waste Committee - January 1977 Meeting, 1976-01-03-1977-04-13 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ARCHO Long-Term Waste Management Committee, 1976-04-1977-01-04 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Includes correspondence, reports, agendas
  - ARCHO - 12th Waste Management Consultants Meeting, 1976-07-13-1976-11-18 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    Includes correspondence, reports, notes, agendas
  - Pall-Trinity-Micro, 1977-1987-04-03 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Includes purchase orders, notes, correspondence, invoices, transparencies, reports
  - Long-Term Nuclear Waste Committee - January 1978 Meeting, 1977-01-09-1978-03-20 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Includes correspondence, agendas, reports
  - Consulting - Merck Sharpe and Dohme, 1977-02-24-1977-02-28 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Includes correspondence, invoice, charts
  - Radioactive Waste Committee 13th Consultants Meeting, 1977-04-07-1977-05-16 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    Includes correspondence, report
  - Radioactive Waste Committee 14th Consultants Meeting, 1977-05-1978-03-21 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Rockwell & Westinghouse Invoices, 1977-08-19-1988-05-16 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Sherwin Williams Company Consulting, 1977-09-28-1978-04-24 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Includes correspondence, notes, invoice
  - DuPont - Department Heads' Meeting, 1978-03-1978-05 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Westinghouse & Rockwell Contracts, 1978-03-17-1988-02-19 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    Includes correspondence, contracts, purchase orders
  - Radioactive Waste Committee 15th Consultants Meeting, 1978-04-1979-02-07 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Long-Term Nuclear Waste Committee - September 1978 Meeting, 1978-05-02-1979-01-17 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Includes briefing, correspondence, notes
  - Long-Term Nuclear Waste Committee - May 1979 Meeting, 1978-11-27-1979-07-26 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Radioactive Waste Committee 16th Consultants Meeting, 1979-05-01-1979-06-07 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - 17th Waste Management Consultants' Meeting, 1979-08-06-1979-12-12 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Includes correspondence, reports, agendas, notes
  - Long-Term Nuclear Waste Committee - February 1980 Meeting, 1979-12-17-1980-05-01 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Rockwell - Review of Waste Site Recovery Report, 1980-03-13 -1980-07-25 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Includes correspondence, notes, reports, invoice
  - Long-Term Nuclear Waste Committee - January 1981 Meeting, 1980-12-03-1982-03-22 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - DuPont CR & D Conference, 1981-06-1981-07 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence, notes, meeting minutes
  - Pfaulder Co., Inc., 1982-08-1982-11 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Includes correspondence, bulletin, proposal
  - Rockwell, 1983-12-01-1985-01-02 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence, meeting minutes, notes, reports, articles
  - Rockwell, 1985-06-28-1986-04-16 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Includes correspondence, notes, reports, agendas
  - Du Pont - Experimental Station, 1985-09-06-1988-12-16 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Includes correspondence, notes, bulletins
  - Rockwell, 1985-11-07-1987-01-21 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Includes correspondence, reports, meeting minutes, notes
  - Rockwell Separation Problem, 1986-03-27-1986-12-03 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lummus, 1986-11-14-1987-10-09 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Includes correspondence, reports, notes, articles
  - Westinghouse & Rockwell, 1986-12-12-1988-07-05 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Solid-Liquid Separation Problems Report, 1986-12-20 (Box 12)
    Prepared for Lummus-Crest, Inc.
  - Consulting - American Cyanamid, 1989-01-18-1991-05-13 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Includes reports, correspondence, notes
  - Cyanamid - Contract, Invoices, 1989-05-11-1992-09-15 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - GE Nuclear Energy Consulting, 1990-09-12-1992-03-02 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Includes map, notes, reports, charts, articles
  - Consulting Inquiry Robinson & Cole, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - GE Report, 1992-01-24-1992-03-16 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Includes transparencies, reports, correspondence
  - GE Consulting, 1992-01-28-1992-12-02 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Includes correspondence, reports, invoice, purchase orders